# JURI CRUZ PSIRICIA VIDEO EDITOR



000

I am a professional video editor from Argentina, living in Denmark with 14 years of experience. I am highly organized, reliable, and adaptable to project needs. I work well independently and thrive in team settings. I am fully available and ready to bring my expertise to your organization.

+45 52 90 97 21



juancruzastradaduran80@gmail.com



Aarhus, Denmark.

## **SOFTWARE**

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Video Editor**

Freelance

Sep 2010 - Now

I have been working as a video editor since I was a kid, editing my own videos as well as for over 50 customers and different social media platforms.

### **Graphic Designer**

Freelance

Jun 2015 - Now

Worked as a Graphic Designer for 9 years, creating thumbnails for videos, wallpapers, etc.

## **EDUCATION**

#### **Bachelor of Multimedia**

Da Vinci Multimedia University Buenos Aires, Argentina

2020 - 2022

Self-taught

2010 - Now

## LANGUAGE

Spanish

100 %

English

90 %

Portuguese

100 %

Danish (Learning)

66 %

